caseyanthony.com 2019-03-04

# Privacy Policy | Casey Anthony

** This privacy policy was last updated March 3, 2017 **

This privacy policy discloses the privacy practices for Casey Anthony at https://caseyanthony.com. This privacy policy applies solely to information collected by this web site.

**<http://it-farmacia.com/informazioni-su-viagra.html> acquistare viagra By visiting CaseyAnthony.com, you acknowledge and accept the practices, terms, and conditions described in this privacy policy and agree that any and all disputes, including, without limitation, those disputes arising over privacy, between you and CaseyAnthony.com, its owners, employees, contributors, advertisers, sponsors, affiliates, partners, and any of their licensees, successors, and assignees, will be subject to terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy**.

**<http://cinziamazzamakeup.com/?x=levitra-generico-20-mg-dose-raccomandata> INFORMATION COLLECTION, USE, AND SHARING**  
We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to, and collect, information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone. We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g. to ship an order. At your sole discretion, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.

**<http://maientertainmentlaw.com/?search=accutane-prices> YOUR ACCESS TO AND CONTROL OVER INFORMATION**  
You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address given on our website:

  * See what data we have about you, if any.
  * Change/correct any data we have about you.
  * Have us delete any data we have about you.
  * Express any concern you have about our use of your data.

**[cialis generico di qualità tadalafil](http://cinziamazzamakeup.com/?x=cialis-generico-di-qualit%C3%A0-tadalafil) CALIFORNIA RESIDENTS PRIVACY RIGHTS**  
California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits our customers who are California residents to request and obtain from us once a year, free of charge, information about the personal information (if any) we disclosed to third parties for direct marketing purposes in the preceding calendar year. If applicable, this information would include a list of the categories of personal information that was shared and the names and addresses of all third parties with which we shared information in the immediately preceding calendar year.  If you are a California resident and would like to make such a request, please submit your request by electronic mail to:[[caseyanthonyblog@gmail.com](mailto:info@perezhilton.com)]

**<http://maientertainmentlaw.com/?search=generic-brand-levitra-buy-online> SECURITY**  
We take reasonable precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline. Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a closed lock icon at the bottom of your web browser, or looking for “https” at the beginning of the address of the web page. While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information.

Our servers are hosted via GoDaddy who you may consult for more detailed information on server security of their WordPress managed sites (https://www.godaddy.com/).  **[source](http://maientertainmentlaw.com/?search=use-of-accutane-durring-alchohol) We cannot and do not guarantee the security of your information in regard to your interactions with our site. Proceed onto this site with this understanding as to our limitations on web and data security. **

**[follow site](http://cinziamazzamakeup.com/?x=miglior-sito-per-comprare-viagra-generico-200-mg-spedizione-veloce-a-Verona) COOKIES**  
We use “cookies” on this site. A cookie is a piece of data stored on a site visitor’s hard drive to help us improve your access to our site and identify repeat visitors to our site. For instance, when we use a cookie to identify you, you would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information on our site.

Some of our business partners may use cookies on our site as a routine process of their business practices (for example, advertisers such as Google AdSense). We have no access to or control over these cookies. Please proceed onto the site accordingly and with fully understanding of this limitation.  
SHARING**  
We may share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person.

We may partner with another party to provide specific services. When the user signs up for these services, we will share names, or other contact information that is necessary for the third party to provide these services. These parties are not allowed to use personally identifiable information except for the purpose of providing these services.  
LINKS**  
This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable information.  
SURVEYS AND CONTESTS**  
From time-to-time our site requests information via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and you may choose whether or not to participate and therefore disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code, age level). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site.

**[quanto costa Viagra generico 25 mg online a Bologna](http://cinziamazzamakeup.com/?x=quanto-costa-Viagra-generico-25-mg-online-a-Bologna) CHILDREN**  
CaseyAnthony.com does not produce content specifically for, or market or advertise specifically to, minors. This is a news and opinion site designed for an adult audience. We rely on a supportive partnership with parents and guardians of minors to caution them from entering the site if they believe the content is inappropriate for their children.

**[new drug like clomid reviews](http://buy-generic-clomid.com/) CONDITIONS OF USE, NOTICES, AND REVISIONS**  
If you choose to visit CaseyAnthony.com, your visit, any subsequent visit, and any dispute over privacy or any other matter related to the site is subject to the terms of this privacy policy which include, among other things, your consent to limitations on any damages you may be entitled to, your agreement to waive any right to a trial you may have and your agreement to arbitrate any disputes, and application of the laws of the State of California. If you have any concern about this privacy policy or the privacy of your personal information at CaseyAnthony.com, please contact us for our attentive review. Unless we specifically state otherwise, the privacy policy applies to all personal information that we may have about you and any related account.

**[before then buy cialis without prescription](http://acrossaday.com/?search=before-then-buy-cialis-without-prescription) UPDATES**  
Our privacy policy may change from time to time and all updates will be posted on this page. We may e-mail periodic reminders of our privacy policy, unless you have instructed us not to, but we are not obligated to do so, and you should check our site frequently to see any changes to any of our privacy policy that may affect you.

**If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately via email: caseyanthonyblog@gmail.com**
